Bamdad Sabet

Senior Software Engineer

+98-9129495183 bamdadsabet@gmail.com linkedin Tehran, Iran Military Service: Exempt

EXPERIENCE

Senior Front-End Engineer

Lisbon, Portugal (Remote)

Fabizi

05/2023 - Present

Fabizi is a rapidly growing startup transforming the food and beverage industry with innovative software solutions that streamline and automate operations for restaurants, cafés, and bars.

- Optimized software architecture, reducing the development-to-production cycle by 50% and cutting bugs by 30%.
- Mentored junior front-end developers, fostering skills, and best practices, and conducting code reviews to ensure quality.
- · Developed complex, user-friendly applications tailored to the food and beverage industry.
- Maintained and improved legacy code to enhance performance and stability.

Software Engineer

Amadeh Laziz

O1/2022 - 06/2023

Amadehlaziz is one of Iran's leading FMCG enterprises, home to renowned brands such as Elit, Copa and many more.

- Advised non-technical departments on software solutions to improve business processes.
- Led recruitment and hiring of software developers and technical talent.
- Developed and implemented custom software solutions to enhance efficiency.
- Developed and managed phone extension and asset management systems.
- Built an online booking and ordering platform for the corporation's café.
- Created survey forms for market research and data collection.
- Contributed to Camunda BPM development for enterprise process management.
- Developed custom object and shell detection systems.

Junior Front-End Developer

Tehran, Iran

01/2021 - 01/2022

Yektanet
Yektanet is the biggest digital marketing agency in Iran.

- Implemented web scraping solutions to extract product data from e-commerce websites.
- · Created scripts to dynamically inject advertisements into web pages.
- · Mentored new team members, providing guidance and support on development tasks.
- Developed responsive and high-converting landing pages.
- Created custom forms for market research and user engagement.
- Developed and optimized email templates for marketing campaigns.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Islamic Azad University, Science And Research Branch

01/2019 - Present

SKILLS

React, Vue, Typescript, Astro, Nuxt, PWA, Pinia, React Query, Redux, Vuetify, Tailwind, Sass

SUMMARY

I'm a Software Engineer with extensive experience working with international clients and agencies.

Familiar with product management methodologies, and I thrive on solving complex problems, learning new technologies, and enjoying a good cup of coffee along the way.

CONTACTS

GitHub

https://github.com/bamdadsabet

Linked In

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bamdad-sabet-946755200

Webiste

https://bamdadsabet.com